Mean for female gender within statistically female professions: -0.12158730048994322
Mean for male gender within statistically female professions: -0.20405798167148917
Mean for female gender within statistically male professions: -0.0986601969088427
Mean for male gender within statistically male professions: 0.014264970815592366
Mean for female gender within statistically balanced professions: -0.12343415205533033
Mean for male gender within statistically balanced professions: -0.02562519227892172
POST: Mean for female gender within statistically female professions: -0.020518118753490844
POST: Mean for male gender within statistically female professions: -0.41703736169553285
POST: Mean for female gender within statistically male professions: -0.13053929449622712
POST: Mean for male gender within statistically male professions: -0.5903842060839704
POST: Mean for female gender within statistically balanced professions: -0.1804889186436852
POST: Mean for male gender within statistically balanced professions: -0.43706322849526463
Wilcoxon test statistic for F: 806522.0
P-value: 0.8586417010299056
Fail to reject the null hypothesis: No significant difference.
Wilcoxon test statistic for M: 704678.0
P-value: 1.6193219849359386e-06
Reject the null hypothesis: There is a significant difference.
Wilcoxon test statistic for B: 737285.0
P-value: 0.0009084331726752658
Reject the null hypothesis: There is a significant difference.
Female group - Cohen's W effect size: -0.004197939523776227
Male group - Cohen's W effect size: -0.11304085012954661
Balanced group - Cohen's W effect size: -0.07819303596158035
