Mean for female gender within statistically female professions: -0.12158551034365454
Mean for male gender within statistically female professions: -0.20405644973024825
Mean for female gender within statistically male professions: -0.09865788751525938
Mean for male gender within statistically male professions: 0.01426779872908772
Mean for female gender within statistically balanced professions: -0.12343221582959481
Mean for male gender within statistically balanced professions: -0.025623071353860022
POST: Mean for female gender within statistically female professions: -0.11812744181413776
POST: Mean for male gender within statistically female professions: -0.28654120043210274
POST: Mean for female gender within statistically male professions: -0.26171007603572133
POST: Mean for male gender within statistically male professions: -0.4372652720939741
POST: Mean for female gender within statistically balanced professions: -0.2224817424119986
POST: Mean for male gender within statistically balanced professions: -0.2562355070150334
Wilcoxon test statistic: 7071679.0
P-value: 0.05518731724884073
Fail to reject the null hypothesis: No significant difference.
Wilcoxon test statistic for F: 781042.0
P-value: 0.18239454027069701
Fail to reject the null hypothesis: No significant difference.
Wilcoxon test statistic for M: 735391.0
P-value: 0.0006657045831557589
Reject the null hypothesis: There is a significant difference.
Wilcoxon test statistic for B: 785889.0
P-value: 0.26543126575416387
Fail to reject the null hypothesis: No significant difference.
Female group - Cohen's W effect size: -0.0314289728908379
Male group - Cohen's W effect size: -0.08021719519224027
Balanced group - Cohen's W effect size: -0.02624887796422299
