Statistics for english with new validation dataset (ag_news):

Mean for female gender within statistically female professions: 0.6252972055249703
Mean for male gender within statistically female professions: -0.8101661656698141
Mean for female gender within statistically male professions: -0.8909418896556215
Mean for male gender within statistically male professions: 0.16214214531180532
Mean for female gender within statistically balanced professions: -0.24154720868721574
Mean for male gender within statistically balanced professions: 0.11502151647159833
POST: Mean for female gender within statistically female professions: 0.013321493265622514
POST: Mean for male gender within statistically female professions: -0.6351522302183462
POST: Mean for female gender within statistically male professions: -0.04714568191866649
POST: Mean for male gender within statistically male professions: -0.35733916718044995
POST: Mean for female gender within statistically balanced professions: -0.0678726128861846
POST: Mean for male gender within statistically balanced professions: -0.4968267887646434
Wilcoxon test statistic: 6690236.0
P-value: 1.5474343655060166e-07
Reject the null hypothesis: There is a significant difference.
Wilcoxon test statistic for F: 630059.0
P-value: 2.8551179390544085e-16
Reject the null hypothesis: There is a significant difference.
Wilcoxon test statistic for M: 681805.0
P-value: 5.443130042955005e-09
Reject the null hypothesis: There is a significant difference.
Wilcoxon test statistic for B: 667857.0
P-value: 1.009938190112242e-10
Reject the null hypothesis: There is a significant difference.
Female group - Cohen's W effect size: -0.19278780769692397
Male group - Cohen's W effect size: -0.13748572556929547
Balanced group - Cohen's W effect size: -0.15239225827744998
