Mean for female gender within statistically female professions: 0.6252924348711484
Mean for male gender within statistically female professions: -0.8101719583734471
Mean for female gender within statistically male professions: -0.8909470790867704
Mean for male gender within statistically male professions: 0.1621358990799197
Mean for female gender within statistically balanced professions: -0.2415514069565976
Mean for male gender within statistically balanced professions: 0.11501611950488058
POST: Mean for female gender within statistically female professions: 0.1183949001400696
POST: Mean for male gender within statistically female professions: -0.7500962457249107
POST: Mean for female gender within statistically male professions: -0.09507461827572888
POST: Mean for male gender within statistically male professions: -0.26791194478133495
POST: Mean for female gender within statistically balanced professions: -0.01254536809780335
POST: Mean for male gender within statistically balanced professions: -0.43409713208214484
Wilcoxon test statistic: 6635251.0
P-value: 1.0236633092971795e-08
Reject the null hypothesis: There is a significant difference.
Wilcoxon test statistic for F: 613237.0
P-value: 3.820596083432061e-19
Reject the null hypothesis: There is a significant difference.
Wilcoxon test statistic for M: 680108.0
P-value: 3.4216847233687407e-09
Reject the null hypothesis: There is a significant difference.
Wilcoxon test statistic for B: 660176.0
P-value: 9.510138819819187e-12
Reject the null hypothesis: There is a significant difference.
Female group - Cohen's W effect size: -0.21076584707293305
Male group - Cohen's W effect size: -0.1392993465906418
Balanced group - Cohen's W effect size: -0.16060111099693195
