Mean for female gender within statistically female professions: 0.49639347400302564
Mean for male gender within statistically female professions: -0.6826802693852245
Mean for female gender within statistically male professions: -0.8324969422894449
Mean for male gender within statistically male professions: 0.15490022708420287
Mean for female gender within statistically balanced professions: -0.3504497785496928
Mean for male gender within statistically balanced professions: 0.050361257426900854
POST: Mean for female gender within statistically female professions: 0.2639104846969677
POST: Mean for male gender within statistically female professions: -0.3714988148118492
POST: Mean for female gender within statistically male professions: 0.22819339316675616
POST: Mean for male gender within statistically male professions: 0.01473161128547105
POST: Mean for female gender within statistically balanced professions: 0.1805973480836078
POST: Mean for male gender within statistically balanced professions: -0.149585798823945
Wilcoxon test statistic: 6024562.0
P-value: 2.0240420411392082e-28
Reject the null hypothesis: There is a significant difference.
Wilcoxon test statistic for F: 768766.0
P-value: 0.05875299300491651
Fail to reject the null hypothesis: No significant difference.
Wilcoxon test statistic for M: 480045.0
P-value: 9.739309049044665e-51
Reject the null hypothesis: There is a significant difference.
Wilcoxon test statistic for B: 685498.0
P-value: 1.4653041651086665e-08
Reject the null hypothesis: There is a significant difference.
Female group - Cohen's W effect size: -0.044548602624513295
Male group - Cohen's W effect size: -0.3531110510064369
Balanced group - Cohen's W effect size: -0.13353893568607106
