Mean for female gender within statistically female professions: 0.6252972055249703
Mean for male gender within statistically female professions: -0.8101661656698141
Mean for female gender within statistically male professions: -0.8909418896556215
Mean for male gender within statistically male professions: 0.16214214531180532
Mean for female gender within statistically balanced professions: -0.24154720868721574
Mean for male gender within statistically balanced professions: 0.11502151647159833
POST: Mean for female gender within statistically female professions: -0.09286612594641407
POST: Mean for male gender within statistically female professions: -0.5811931041274582
POST: Mean for female gender within statistically male professions: -0.1321876839011532
POST: Mean for male gender within statistically male professions: -0.16499534744222763
POST: Mean for female gender within statistically balanced professions: -0.14567200598794014
POST: Mean for male gender within statistically balanced professions: -0.3005063707966106
Wilcoxon test statistic: 6758107.0
P-value: 3.2490641411571617e-06
Reject the null hypothesis: There is a significant difference.
Wilcoxon test statistic for F: 620048.0
P-value: 5.965219447024355e-18
Reject the null hypothesis: There is a significant difference.
Wilcoxon test statistic for M: 644898.0
P-value: 6.074601823071665e-14
Reject the null hypothesis: There is a significant difference.
Wilcoxon test statistic for B: 673046.0
P-value: 4.659109631382328e-10
Reject the null hypothesis: There is a significant difference.
Female group - Cohen's W effect size: -0.20348678238443
Male group - Cohen's W effect size: -0.17692904379842206
Balanced group - Cohen's W effect size: -0.1468466604696916
