Mean for female gender within statistically female professions: 0.6252972055249703
Mean for male gender within statistically female professions: -0.8101661656698141
Mean for female gender within statistically male professions: -0.8909418896556215
Mean for male gender within statistically male professions: 0.16214214531180532
Mean for female gender within statistically balanced professions: -0.24154720868721574
Mean for male gender within statistically balanced professions: 0.11502151647159833
POST: Mean for female gender within statistically female professions: 0.17642072067351094
POST: Mean for male gender within statistically female professions: -0.49572748313427356
POST: Mean for female gender within statistically male professions: 0.004527144614337541
POST: Mean for male gender within statistically male professions: -0.21907641154985052
POST: Mean for female gender within statistically balanced professions: 0.05940318406406056
POST: Mean for male gender within statistically balanced professions: -0.29785712765820305
Wilcoxon test statistic: 7055711.0
P-value: 0.03970784866153301
Reject the null hypothesis: There is a significant difference.
Wilcoxon test statistic for F: 714881.0
P-value: 1.4689581353946714e-05
Reject the null hypothesis: There is a significant difference.
Wilcoxon test statistic for M: 604054.0
P-value: 8.094295895231256e-21
Reject the null hypothesis: There is a significant difference.
Wilcoxon test statistic for B: 780536.0
P-value: 0.1749841899395742
Fail to reject the null hypothesis: No significant difference.
Female group - Cohen's W effect size: -0.10213668084210034
Male group - Cohen's W effect size: -0.22057992004819704
Balanced group - Cohen's W effect size: -0.031969746159430254
