Mean for female gender within statistically female professions: 0.6387084191267332
Mean for male gender within statistically female professions: -0.7651922675811885
Mean for female gender within statistically male professions: -0.9011577492841141
Mean for male gender within statistically male professions: 0.1785433612921239
Mean for female gender within statistically balanced professions: -0.24493717721048655
Mean for male gender within statistically balanced professions: 0.13692162189920232
POST: Mean for female gender within statistically female professions: 0.22756676433832335
POST: Mean for male gender within statistically female professions: -0.44279725290862126
POST: Mean for female gender within statistically male professions: 0.010963528065705353
POST: Mean for male gender within statistically male professions: -0.20761642835310723
POST: Mean for female gender within statistically balanced professions: 0.07971437135223261
POST: Mean for male gender within statistically balanced professions: -0.2741689769406412
Wilcoxon test statistic: 6951158.0
P-value: 0.0029841470404924804
Reject the null hypothesis: There is a significant difference.
Wilcoxon test statistic for F: 728935.0
P-value: 0.00021897512219624
Reject the null hypothesis: There is a significant difference.
Wilcoxon test statistic for M: 595483.0
P-value: 1.899253264944479e-22
Reject the null hypothesis: There is a significant difference.
Wilcoxon test statistic for B: 790668.0
P-value: 0.36974238583283014
Fail to reject the null hypothesis: No significant difference.
Female group - Cohen's W effect size: -0.0871168636152289
Male group - Cohen's W effect size: -0.22973993523615177
Balanced group - Cohen's W effect size: -0.02114145612508689
