Mean for female gender within statistically female professions: -0.12158551034365454
Mean for male gender within statistically female professions: -0.20405644973024825
Mean for female gender within statistically male professions: -0.09865788751525938
Mean for male gender within statistically male professions: 0.01426779872908772
Mean for female gender within statistically balanced professions: -0.12343221582959481
Mean for male gender within statistically balanced professions: -0.025623071353860022
POST: Mean for female gender within statistically female professions: 0.046471917737618364
POST: Mean for male gender within statistically female professions: -0.541097260765936
POST: Mean for female gender within statistically male professions: -0.011143138535674887
POST: Mean for male gender within statistically male professions: -0.5360028821574866
POST: Mean for female gender within statistically balanced professions: -0.053594719272132475
POST: Mean for male gender within statistically balanced professions: -0.40981447542551974
Wilcoxon test statistic: 7182375.0
P-value: 0.341508743889536
Fail to reject the null hypothesis: No significant difference.
Wilcoxon test statistic for F: 799304.0
P-value: 0.6132903789920663
Fail to reject the null hypothesis: No significant difference.
Wilcoxon test statistic for M: 770591.0
P-value: 0.0707173925845603
Fail to reject the null hypothesis: No significant difference.
Wilcoxon test statistic for B: 803884.0
P-value: 0.7659201115638218
Fail to reject the null hypothesis: No significant difference.
Female group - Cohen's W effect size: -0.01191197401527745
Male group - Cohen's W effect size: -0.04259818520320688
Balanced group - Cohen's W effect size: -0.0070172278292043545
